Contact

+91 8860301488 (Mobile) mcgupthebany@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mayankgupta-07539924 (LinkedIn) www.tobehealthy.me (Company)

Top Skills

Business Strategy
Program Management
Financial Modeling

Mayank Gupta

Founder & CEO, To Be Honest

Greater Delhi Area

Summary

Experienced Founder with a demonstrated history of working in the food & beverages industry. Skilled in Entrepreneurship, Start-ups, Project Management, Financial Modeling, and Product Development. Strong business development professional with a PGDM focused in Flnance and Marketing from Indian Institute of Management, Lucknow.

Experience

To Be Honest Founder September 2015 - Present (5 years) A 47, Sector 67 Noida 201301

To Be Honest is an innovative F&B brand based out of Delhi NCR. To Be Honest is constantly working with nutritionists to develop a wholesome offering with one goal in mind - to deliver delicious and nutritious products to the consumers.

Pyro Power Co-Founder June 2011 - January 2015 (3 years 8 months) New Delhi Area, India

Pyro Power is offering products and services in the Renewable Energy Sector, specialising in the Solar, wind and fuel cell technologies.

As the CEO, was incharge of Business development, Project Finance, Project planing and financial modeling.

Education

Indian Institute of Management, Lucknow PGDM, Flnance and Marketing (2008 - 2010)

Delhi College of Engineering

BE, Electronics and Comunication · (2003 - 2007)